They was all over the wall
Where can we go from his present?
Where South not
Alleluia
We want to start on a lesson from the book of Mark
Because of the world believe you understand it better in these tests
in the book of mark 16
verse 17 and
this I
Will follow those who believe in my name
They will cast out what
The what believing is what we want to talk about now
if you believe
those same
Shall follow you
Shall be yours
We take a potato at lean on the way
Let us say acting on the word
That's jolly well believing believing
Demise
action
creates action it
requires performance
So yes, I'm a good player. Okay. Yeah group layer. Let's go to the feet
Show yourself. You're a good player
Yeah, cupola is not word of mouth. You go to the feed and show yourself perform
girls wear
Reflects is kurata
- well
Reflects is what is Kurata
So when you say believe you talk of action
Action, this was his law choice deliver change
I'm a shadow go change why mental arson admins?
Admirers
But does not act
Acting on the way
Is letting Christ Act rule because Christ and the we're a one
It does slotting without what?
Without his we're through this were buying spirit
Tell you're never letting the where
half right of way
In your life
Is letting Christ
Have right of way
Because Christ and the where I wanna
Tell you never let it be where half right of way
In your life
Is letting Christ
Half right of way
It is the way dueling you
Which is equivalent to Christ personally being in you
Tell them or acting on the wedge
It is the we're doing live in you
Which is equivalent to Christ Osmel a being in you
Christ and the way I won't
Let you take you to the book of James
James one
was twenty-two day be du'a of the world and not here are only
Be dua of the world are not here only
Disable yourself
for if anyone is a hearer of the word and
Not a doer
He is like a man observing
his natural face in a mirror
24 for e observes himself
Goes away and immediately forgets what kind of man he was
Acting on the way
then
Gives her an opportunity
to do all to heal you
To bless you
To save you to deliver you to touch you
Given the way its place
Is giving
Christ
Is position of law silly? I mean the way dominating you
In the lordship of Christ in you
The way dominating you is the lordship of Christ you
The problem of believing
Is made simple
When we know that it is acting on what goddess porking
The problem of believing because that's the problem we're Christian I have on today
Processing you cannot be greater than your processing?
The way I dress in the room is the way I look now
The way I combed my hair is a way and look mom
Tell about you cannot be greater than your processing
So believing is like a gradient
When you are making a soup
You put a gradient
Processing
When one means you miss all
you want to say one plus one plus one is equal to three, but you know say one plus one plus one you say for
Something's wrong somewhere
The problem of believing is made simple
Well, we know that it is acting on what God has working
Love your neighbor as yourself. That is God. I'm going to utter that. I'm going to love my neighbor as myself
humble
For Gracia, my humility this time is not for selfish classic and materiality
humility for gossip
I'm going to be faithful
for God's sake
The wise man is the dryer of the world the other years
But does not act upon it
He is a sense knowledge here on
His mental assent
Because he respond
To listen instead of the Word of God
He is a mentor Ascenta
He respond
to listen
instead of war
instead of the weather girl
Their faculty is the one that dictate the direction
When they are sick they
Pray for healing
when they are poor they pray for
blessing
When they are blessed they say thank you Jesus
The Association audited the direction of the wall of the aprea
If Chase is alright you see them dance in the shot thank you Jesus. Thank you Jesus and we'll sit and know that
Your situation is the one that detect the direction of your prayer. We will not allow you to be free
You continue to complain and complain and complain and complain you will not want you to say thank you Jesus for one day
Tell anyone if Satan
know
That your situation is the one detect the direction of your prayer
He will not allow you to
Say, thank you Jesus
The weight of the say lady will say I'm
Lettuce Excel
You would never hear them say that was wrong. I'm sick. Now. I can assume he when they have not pray for me
Let the poor son bless
I've not gone home to do business to get money
dissemblers
know
he
respond to listen instead of war
the Word of God
By his tribes I can hear you
He
If he has faith in anything
It is a man what man has done?
science
works
organization and so for this attitude II have fit in and that
Is all about fact not truth because take a change, but the weather girl is saying truth
If he has faith in anything it is in mom
Look at that company wonderful. I want to be like that man. How can you be like a man?
No, you can't be like that man
That is imitation. That is imitation
We know the words
Say this is the word of God and what we are talking about is on the myths of the Bible
Abilities we may be familiar to the original Greek or Hebrew
We may know the history of the world
But that is all
Business wasted energy
If you do not act on the word
if you do not lead the way and
practice it
If we do not live the way and practice it
We cannot bring Jesus on the same
Josh prayer is a reality. We are not talking into the air
Prayer is a reality
When they behave be deliver here
The name Jesus is always horrid. If you act on the word the ninjas or is a lesson on
What a grave danger of
deluding ourselves
The seven of us a
What a danger if there is no corresponding actions
If we say in the name of Jesus
Without corresponding Asia, it will be I do
Meaningless and awful time destructive
It is the doer of the word
that receives change from God I do where's
Mae Etta ten men they do knowledge God
Tell you what it is they do of the way
That received him from God I do where me at attend man
They do not reach God
Open the book of it efficiently
verse 20 now
To him who is able to do
exceedingly abundantly above
All that we ask or team today today
We ask or think
according to the power that we work
in us
They say where that control details there. Let's read together now
To him who is able to do or the lady?
What do if you remove dude the whole way is useless? How can I do is that's the question?
It is going to be according to
the ability of God
That is at war in us
What is the ability you are here today because
You are energized by Christ
You walk freely you talk freely you sit down freely you listen to me freely
There are many people on the seabed they want to be here, but they are not energized
Saleable I'm here today because I'm in a giant
by cried Jesus
It is going to be
according to the
ability of
God that is at war within us you say which abilities of God that is at work within me. I
Don't have any ability because I cannot hear I don't have an ability because I cannot see live
First call in turn one
The static but of him you are in Christ Jesus who?
Became for us wisdom from God
righteousness and sanctification and redemption
You have him as your wisdom he is your redemption as well a
Redemption for your witness
And your failure and your lack of ability and ignorance?
Terrible I have him
As my wisdom I can hear you
Here's my Redemption as well a redemption for my witness and my
Failure and my lack of ability and ignorance
When you are we then you are strong
What does that mean?
Yes witness
There's a strength all this with me before me after me behind me. I
Have him as my wisdom as my strength
He is my Redemption a
Redemption for my witness and my
Failure and my lack of ability and ignorance
Let me come to the end of this message let's look at the book of collision 1 verse 9
We have such knowledge
Complete knowledge
That knowledge
Is in the wedge
There are so much demising. I'm looking forward. I'm looking for processor
You are looking for a city where?
We have such knowledge is
Knowledge
complete knowledge
Perfect knowledge that knowledge is in the world
What you are demanded for is in the word
Illumined by the Spirit we
Were
Illumined by the spirit
The counter gadgets
When the word gets into a broad
Gain supremacy over the conspiracy Aspira stick
In conclusion we'll have a
Sat knowledge
exact wisdom
exact blessing
Exact virtual just name them
What you are looking for tell you all about what you are looking for
What you are searching for
Is in the word
Tell about that money you are looking for is in the word that
Possession you are looking for it's in the where?
Authority you are looking for it's in the well, it's in the well
proceed
same
polarity
Good hair
Hilly breath true you are looking for it's in the where you want to become president of nature
scimitar I
Can hear you?
It's in the where's thank you
By the Holy Ghost and just ask the professor
This is the day of the lottery
God it's moving its bar again
by
Anointing Jesus praise
You he's no bite ha
He's not by my
By my speed
Oh
Yeah